10 years 50 years
whatever is left in your life that's how
long you have until the time
before you know
that's really when your right is decided
for eternity yes
yes
well I hope I don't confuse the issue
so it's actually a lot of times yeah
but you know these very important
stations we discuss with with other
people like execution
the Christians and others and some of us
can say
let's suppose a man leaves five thousand
years
before judgment
suppose at the end of the world is
the year 2000.
what was happening to him you see how
they are it's very interesting what was
happening to him
so
seven no yeah what was happening to him
those seven thousand years
it seems to to make sense
and so people have to invent limbo or a
kind of purgatory for people at all
places like in a like a big waste basket
when somebody dies Allah puts it in a
way back a lot about that in all the
thousands of his past he collects them
and then he judges all of them I think
this is the very wrong way of looking at
his life because if we found the Quran
we must not use our time dimension
before Allah
is not the same this already shows
we must not
look at the day of resolution in terms
of our birthday time Dimensions that is
and it's been emphasized in our group
before Allah Resurrection has already
taken place and people already have gone
to heaven and have gone to to hell all
right but to us we'll start to our
material world
we are thinking of those who died
thousand five thousand years and maybe
those who release the next so many
thousand years but from the point of
view of
from another point of view
if
if the resurrection is like one night or
like a blink of an eye after our death
then we don't ask anybody question what
happens to those who have been alive and
who have died five thousand years ago
Quran says very clearly in the other
religions also say that the final
Judgment of the last hour is for
everyone it seems to be inconsistent
with the fact that people die is equal
centuries but not the way the Quran
explains it
Quran assumes
it is one final
judgment one final hour and yet
between the time of our death and that
is at the beginning of
life and so on and I think that's being
to me that's the meaning of the verse
that it is nearer than what we think it
is because to many people Facebook says
well I'll die now and suppose the world
we still exist for 20 000 years I will
be in lingo for 20 000 years except for
the quranisms
but no the currency is no it's nearer
and so people are expecting for it
anytime now Christ himself said that the
hour is near at hand and people
were waiting the year 1000 everybody
thought is going to be the last judgment
and you're waiting year 2000 everybody
will wait for it
because the thing near in the sense of
you
that it is the the Quran is very true
where it starts sugar that's the
relativity of time between we and our
ancestors
and we in our future descendants
and the time between our lives now and
the year Hereafter but the way this uh
the Quran expressive I think all these
difficult things are done I mean we need
that we need not ask the question
anymore
from the time we die in the last hour
how many thousands of years it will take
place and I think Islam is the only
reason that has given these answers as
far as I know my studies of comparative
religion
before
right but as far as we're concerned and
the people who died a long time ago is
to invest in Resurrection there is no
time
so people
us you know we asleep wake up sleep wake
up sleep wake up the driveway so there's
no difference between sleeping
in fact people don't know that they died
John Kennedy is doesn't know anybody
you know yeah
[Music]
it's a it's a frog
they have to be clinically dead
yourself
today
well there was another there was a
number of rich people who have the
bodies Frozen
because that's what Angela's talking
about they're waiting for scientific
advances that will have
uh that can solve the diseases of the
fuel that these diseases and one of the
big one of these victims had a power
breakdown where all the bodies saw and
the relatives the relatives are suing
you ride the rocket and go outside the
Earth's atmosphere it's not like 50
miles from here
then there's no night there's no day
there's no hour
there's no there's no time
unless you want to use your heart like a
block or something
as soon as you leave the reason we have
nice and day here is that the sun is now
on the other side of the earth and we
are in the same
but if you leave the planet Earth
there's no time
just just to add something to that
relativity physics teachers that called
clock okay
this length of a second is not fixed it
depends on the speed that it's going and
the old you know the old analogy is if
somebody is 27 years old and he could go
close to the speed of light for 50 years
and then come back to the Earth it would
be thousands of years later so the the
idea of the Common Sense idea of time be
just being duration being something big
it's confirmed by the the old occult
doctors and the corals we have only 26
minutes
foreign
came back
so it doesn't matter what kind of uh
comes back
because if he dies he doesn't know and
when he opens his eyes the dead
resurrection and he looks for the
Baptist the operations assistant
what happened to my kids
it's not funny
it's gonna be a shocker for the
disbelief
um
then they already know being that there
was a student of course they should know
if that's what the angel is supposed to
say all this kind of stuff or whatever
on the day of judgment I'm saying
you're welcome in you okay but what I'm
what I'm thinking
um no but you talk about the engines the
communicating on this actually you're
resurrected that's what you're talking
about if they die on the tables
okay and what I'm saying is like we know
we well we have an idea what it's going
to be like going to be our Resurrection
but then we also fear that
and I was just wondering who we know
you'll be afraid and forget I mean
no
I'm just wondering if they're going to
be so right but they're still going to
be you know so afraid of Allah because
still we don't know if we're Believers
or not even though
yeah
when you open your eyes you'll know that
you're gone to me
moment
don't worry you look at your size
yeah
oh okay okay
and then the record
or
you know I mean you know what I'm saying
do you get the breakfast person
um
everybody's record would be
we will apply to your neck I mean this
is just a symbolic now you will have
you'll have your record really
okay
you know give you some type of ideas
are all symbolic but if you look up to
17 it will tell you about the 2017
the number is 13.
page 188
188.
verse 1 3.
under the subtitle the video record
says we have the record that every human
being tries to his neck
then under their Resurrection we will
give him a record that he will find
accessible
read your record today you suffice as
reckoners for yourself so you'll be a
result in other words
so that record that you'll find the
video records of your life from birth to
death will explain to you why you are in
this position whatever position you find
yourself
so that record will simply explain to
you why
so then that other person just